This is the basis for 8 years of dancing.
Now.
All this time?
Please make a note of these two cases as well.
Yes, I will. I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, I will. So, let's continue the topic from the first part.
Okay, let's talk about MIU.
Now, I would like to do the Staplerfest.
We belong to Stapler, right?
That's right.
Staff Pro Fest.
We also received the Cinderella Group at the Staff ProFest held in January this year,
Thank you very much.
At the last Staff ProFest, one of our members, Karin Tachibana, was chosen as a Cinderella,
This is the second year in a row.
It's the second year in a row.
Two awards.
Yes, that's right.
I apologize.
Two championships.
He's strong in every competition.
That's right.
The Staff Pro Fest has been a mainstream competition,
We fought every time,
There were two individual battles and one group battle,
But Tohoku-san is not too competitive.
I think people have an image of Tōhoku-san as being tough,
To tell the truth,
But to tell you the truth, they are not like that.
That's right.
He doesn't like to compete.
It's a little bit NG.
But..,
If we're going to do it, let's win,
If we are going to do it, let's win, right?
So, I am a pacifist who does not really want to fight,So I am a pacifist who doesn't really want to fight too much,
I'm a Northeasterner, you know.
But the manager is very passionate.
I see.
If we're going to do it, we have to do it.
You guys have to do it.
He was really pressuring us to be good at what we do,
Let me tell you an episode,
This year's StarPlaza festival had a cinerary group event,
Running?
Dash?
It's like a field day, but not a field day,
It's not a sports day, but they played competitive basketball,
That's right.
We also played kendama.
The final event was the dash.
I'm going to be in the dash, right?
And Yuna watching over them,
And then there was the manager,
The manager who accompanied Rine to practice,
And the manager who accompanied Rine to practice was right in front of Yeye.
Yes, that's right. So, they were practicing by finding a normal path of
Dash.
Rine and the manager.
This is the manager.
This is Rine.
This is Rin and Rinwaka.
We ran to the start.
Rinne ran and ran,
The manager got a little burned.
Ouch!
She struggled.
That much?
Hurts!
Where does it hurt?
It hurts here.
Here?Here?
It hurts!
Are you okay?
I got in the car and said, "This is really bad.
I went to the hospital.
To my surprise, I had broken my sakos.
When you have a manager who is that stubborn,
We had no choice but to win,
If the manager broke a bone, we have to get that bone back.
We had to win.
We took the Cinderella Group.
Even now, there's a hard board in there.
A hard board.
Please take care of yourself.
I had just broken my leg during the rehearsal for the Supapla festival,
Don't let someone hit you from behind,
I put a sign on the front of the back of the room saying that I had a broken bone,
I got a lot of compliments from the cute girls in the staff group,
Are you okay?
In a way, I thought that was an enviable strategy.
I think it's a good thing that I won until I was injured.
So, that was the theme of the staff festival.
I would like to continue.
I'm going to deliver it live!
And this one, too. The board on the baest.
We have been doing a number of live broadcasts, and recently, I have been doing a 19-hour live broadcast on Yo UTube, the official YouTube site of Mr. Makoto Kusama.
Before the 19-hour distribution, I distributed for 12 hours.
Before that, he did a 12-hour stream. Before that, I delivered for 7 hours, and the number of long-time delivery has been gradually increasing. The number of long-time delivery has been gradually increasing.
But it's quite a big deal to follow an idol for 19 hours, isn't it? I think it's quite a hard thing to do. You have to smile the whole time.
But we were not trying to show all of our true nature, but we were trying to show the natural fun of the idols.
I think this is possible because of everyone's mindset. I think this is something that only Tomoku-san can do, or rather, something that only Tomoku-san can do.
The other day, we all went glamping, camping, barbecuing, cheese making, and moss making.
We went to a glamping camp, barbecued, made cheese, and made moss. We had a campfire. They had a campfire, mime, and the leader cried. They were so happy that they cried. The leader cried because he was so happy to mime with everyone.
We managed to deliver for 19 hours, but in the past, we have done a lot of different kinds of delivery.
When we first formed, we were doing Tweakath for a long time, and we were definitely learning how to do food reportage on Tweakath.
We were definitely learning how to do that food reportage on the tweets. We were still just baby idols, so we didn't know much about food lipo.
But we were still baby idols, so we didn't know what food lipo was. We were eating normally outside the screen. We let it slide at the time, but after the distribution was overEveryone eats together, you know. And they were eating off-screen. I let it slide at the time, but after the distribution was over, the manager was furious with me to death.
But after the distribution was over, I was scolded by the manager to death. Why did you guys eat off-screen?
He told me to eat when the camera was pointed at me and give my first reaction.
But you don't know that, do you? So I was really pissed off, and I was so disappointed and traumatized by the food reportage that I was a little afraid of it.
I was even traumatized by the experience of being afraid of food reportage, but through these experiences, I grew up to be able to deliver such a long-time reportage.
I have grown up to be able to deliver such a long time.
So, we have the tools to do this now.
Soon, we'll have the tools...
Well, there it is, there it is, there it is.
me
We've been doing a lot of tours.
What's the first tour? Live music club tour?
We did a live house tour in Tohoku and a world tour.
We also did a world tour.
The world tour is a tour of amusement parks.
It's not really an overseas tour, but a tour of amusement parks in faraway places that are made to look like amusement parks.
There is an amusement park called Cha Cha World.
or Bennyland called Lina World.
and so on.
The same goes for the tour where we don't go to Tokyo.
And this year, we did a nationwide tour called "We'll Never Lose".
The scale of the tour is getting bigger and bigger.
We've done a lot of tours.
We've done a lot of tours, and we've traveled by air, by bullet train
or by bullet train or by Hiace.
But this tour was different.
For the first time, the costumes were made for the tour.
There was also a quick change of clothes.
There was a performance in every costume.
There was a box
For each song, the members would move the box with different eyes
The members would move the box with different eyes for each song and change the direction.
We've done many tours.
How many tours have you done? This year?
You've done 21 shows and made it a success.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's been a while.It's been a while.
Thank you very much.
By touring, I've been able to visit new places for the first time.
I've been able to have a lot of satellites.
It's great to have the opportunity to go to the countryside, isn't it?
The food that we eat at the satellite sites is really good.
We love to eat together.
There's not a day that goes by that we don't eat.
That's for sure.
We eat local food together.
We have fun while doing satellite work.
My manager's dream is to be a baseball fan.
Not only professional baseball, but also the Koshien Stadium.
Every year around this time, the Koshien Stadium is held.
Every year around this time, there's the Koshien Stadium, and she wants to go to the prefecture that wins the championship.
For my family.
My family members go to that prefecture for that reason alone.
Every year, there is an event to congratulate the winner of the championship.
I wonder where we can go this year.
I don't know if I can go there or not.
Last year, it was Tokushima or Sendai.
Last year, Sendai won the championship, so they held a live concert in their hometown.
Maybe there are people from Tokushima.
Draft, huh?
I went to Tokushima because Koshien was not held in Corona.
It's not the name of the players, but the names of the 47 prefectures in Japan.
They drew the name of the prefecture and said the player would go to that prefecture.
So they drew the names of the 47 prefectures, and the player went to Tokushima.
I'm doing this on my own.
Last year, Sendai won the championship.
We've had Koshien championship events in the past, right?
There was a little incident here.
It's a little incident.
The event for the winner of the championship.
It's got the name "00" in it.
A phone call came in.
00 championship event00Winning Event
Shall we do it? I've decided to do it.
We decided to do it and changed it to a championship event last year.
I'm sorry.
Please put a "P" in it.
P!
It's a congratulations event for the winners.
Yes, it is.
That's right. There was such an incident, wasn't there?
Yes, there was. So, that's all for today,
That's all for today, the second one,
What a surprise, there will be another one tomorrow.
Oh, my God!
Three tailoring.
Three. It's gorgeous, isn't it?
It's a special, gorgeous event.
Please look forward to seeing you all tomorrow.
Now, let's see who we have so far.
Ujiran!
Inari.
I'm sorry.
It seems like these things have happened.
Yes, it has.
This is our 8th anniversary so far.
So, who have you been with so far?
Ujiran!
Sunday's star last!
Mr. Hinari Talk's
Waka Yasumori and
Mie Fujitani.
See you tomorrow.
Afterimage. Afterimage.